{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Portugal",
    "predicate": "property/event",
    "object": "resource/Portuguese_Restoration_War",
    "human_readable": "The Kingdom of Portugal was involved in the Portuguese Restoration War.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9644491672515869,
            "question": "Was Portugal a participant in the Portuguese Restoration War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9471375942230225,
            "question": "Which country's restoration war did Portugal participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9388884902000427,
            "question": "What war was the Kingdom of Portugal involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9049350619316101,
            "question": "Why was the Kingdom of Portugal involved in war?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8176018595695496,
            "question": "What was the name of the war that led to the restoration of the Portuguese monarchy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8048428297042847,
            "question": "In what century did the Portuguese Restoration War take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7670252323150635,
            "question": "Who were the opposing sides in the Portuguese Restoration War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7323988080024719,
            "question": "What were the consequences of the Portuguese Restoration War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6723893284797668,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a significant event during the Portuguese Restoration War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48828378319740295,
            "question": "What historical conflict is associated with Portugal?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Kingdom of Portugal was involved in the Portuguese Restoration War.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8736_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a significant event during the Portuguese Restoration War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8736_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the consequences of the Portuguese Restoration War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8736_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the opposing sides in the Portuguese Restoration War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8736_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8736_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: According to the document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8736/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt, it mentions that \"The Portuguese Restoration War (1640-1668) was a struggle to regain independence from Spain.\" and also mentions that \"After the Portuguese Restoration War of 1640\u20131668, the kingdom passed to the House of Braganza...\" This suggests that the Kingdom of Portugal was indeed involved in the Portuguese Restoration War."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe context information provided clearly mentions that the \"Portuguese Restoration War (1640-1668) was a struggle to regain independence from Spain,\" which directly supports the statement that \"The Kingdom of Portugal was involved in the Portuguese Restoration War.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}